William N. Fenton Papers 1933-2000 Mss.Ms.Coll.20
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1897-1994; 39 boxes; 19.25 linear feet
  - Bachrach, Deborah, 1986 (Box Series I-2)
    Museum of the American Indian
  - Bahr, Donald M., 1992 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bailey, Alfred G., 1939-1944, 1976 (Box Series I-2)
    McCrum, Blanche Prichard
  - Bailey, David W., 1945 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bailey, Edna, 1968 (Box Series I-2)
  - Bailey, Nicodemus, 1939, 1960, 1965 (Box Series I-2)
    -See also Ser. I, Holmes, Oliver Wendell
  - Baldus, Herbert, 1953-1954 (Box Series I-2)
  - Baligadoo, Urszula Chodowiec, 1969-1980 (Box Series I-2)
  - Banko, Walter M., 1988 (Box Series I-3)
    -For photos., See Ser. VI, False Face (Six Nations Reserve, Caledonia 1988)
  - Barbeau, C. Marius, 1939-1967 (Box Series I-3)
    Canada Council
    Canadian Social Science Research Council
    Chafe, Wallace L.
    Desrosiers, Leo-Paul
    Elliott, Flavia
    National Museum of Canada
    -See also Ser. I, Bridges, Marjorie Lismer
  - Barber, Daniel M., 1966 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barck, Dorothy C. (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, New-York Historical Society
  - Barker, E. Gilbert, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barner, Jennifer C., 1989 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barnes, Millie Jo, 1968 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barnes, Stanley N., 1942 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barnett, [H.G.], 1945 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barnouw, Victor, 1949 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barrett, S.A., 1964 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barrus, George Latta, 1960 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barse, Reva Cooper, 1944-1948 (Box Series I-3)
  - Barthold, Allen J., 1944 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bartholomew, David (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, Cornplanter, Jesse J.
  - Bartlett, Charles E., 1955-1960 (Box Series I-3)
    -See also Ser. I, Cornplanter, Jesse J.
    -See also Ser. I, Liesinger, Rudolph O.
  - Bartlett, Charles E., Jr., 1978 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bartlett, Sally (Box Series I-3)
  - Barton, William O. (Mrs.), 1966 (Box Series I-3)
  - Basa, Louise, 1974 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bascom, William R., 1949 (Box Series I-3)
  - Basehart, Harry W., 1941-1971 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bates, Erl, 1961 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bauman, Frederick, 1990 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bausor, S.C., 1943 (Box Series I-3)
  - Beachamp, William M. (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, Corning, Erastus II
  - Beals, Ralph L., 1946, 1969 (Box Series I-3)
    Goldschmidt, Walter
  - Bean, Lowell J., 1970 (Box Series I-3)
  - Beatty, Willard W., 1940-1941 (Box Series I-3)
  - Béchard, Henri, 1979 (Box Series I-3)
  - Becker, Howard, 1946 (Box Series I-3)
  - Becker, Marshall Joseph, 1976, 1990 (Box Series I-3)
    Spada, Albert
  - Becker, Mary A. Druke (Box Series I-3)
    -See also Ser. I, Jennings, Francis P.
    -See also Ser. IIb, Iroquois Documentary History Project
    - Folder #1, 1973-May 1979 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder #2, Jun. 1979-1980 (Box Series I-3)
    - Folder #3, 1981-1993 (Box Series I-3)
  - Becker-Donner, Etta, 1953, 1957 (Box Series I-3)
  - Beecher, Willis J., 1905 (Box Series I-3)
    Starr, Frederick
  - Bell, Earl H. (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, Snyderman, George S.
  - Bell, R. Murray (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, Champlain Society
  - Bell, Robert E., 1951, 1953 (Box Series I-3)
  - Benedict, Ernest, 1940-1941 (Box Series I-3)
  - Benezet, Louis, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-3)
  - Benham, Floyd H., 1949 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bercker, Paul, 1959 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berkhofer, Robert, 1980 (Box Series I-3)
  - Berry, C.H., 1941 (Box Series I-3)
    -See also Ser. I, Deardorff, Merle H.
  - Berry, Rose V.S., 1940 (Box Series I-3)
  - Best, Elsdon, 1975 (Box Series I-3)
    Morgan, L.H.
  - Bethlehem Public Library, 1988 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bethune, Anne B., 1945 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bettarel, Robert (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, Straight, Stephen M.
  - Bharati, Agehananda, 1972 (Box Series I-3)
  - Biddle, Martin, 1977 (Box Series I-3)
  - Biedermann, Hans, 1962 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bierhorst, John, 1973, 1987-1993 (Box Series I-3)
    Smithsonian Institution
  - Bigler, Eugene (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, Cornplanter, Jesse J. (1951)
  - Bihler, Hugh J., 1969 (Box Series I-3)
  - Billet, James, 1970-1971 (Box Series I-3)
  - Billington, Ray Allen, 1969, 1980 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bishop, Charles A., 1971, 1977 (Box Series I-3)
  - Bishop, Morris, 1949 (Box Series I-3)
    -See also Ser. I, Stewart, Alexander
  - Bishop Museum, 1975, 1980 (Box Series I-3)
    Force, Roland W.
    -See also Ser. I, Moorhead, M.J.
  - Blackfeet Tribal Business Council (Box Series I-3)
    -See Ser. I, Fickinger, Paul L.
  - Blackwood, Beatrice M., 1955-1968 (Box Series I-3)
    Pitt Rivers Museum
  - Blakely, Stuart B., 1949 (Box Series I-3)
  - Blaker, Margaret C. (Box Series I-3)
  - Blanchard, David, 1979 (Box Series I-4)
  - Blankenship, Roy, 1977-1993 (Box Series I-4)
    University of Pennsylvania Press
  - Blau, Harold, 1967-1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bleimeyer, Rose T., 1939 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bliss, Wesley L., 1942-1943 (Box Series I-4)
  - Blitzer, Charles (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, American Folklore Society, Inc.
  - Bloomfield, Leonard, 1943, 1945 (Box Series I-4)
  - Blue, Jamie, 1987 (Box Series I-4)
  - B'nai B'rith (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, Anti-Defamation League of B'nai B'rith
  - Boas, Franz, 1933 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bobrinskoy, Theodora Platt, 1948 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bodine, John J., 1963 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bodleian Library, 1966 (Box Series I-4)
  - Boggs, Stephen T. (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, American Anthropological Association
    -See Ser. I, Krader, Lawrence
  - Bogyi, A.M. (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, Noakes, G.T.
  - Bohannon, Paul J., 1966 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bolton, Jacklin T., 1963 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bomberry, Evelyn, 1977-1978 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bomberry, Walter (Mrs.), 1943 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bond, Richmond P., 1947-1948 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bonos, Constantine A. (Mrs.), 1940 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bonvillain, Nancy, 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bookman, George B., 1972 (Box Series I-4)
  - Borhegyi, Stephan F., 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bosch-Gimpera, P., 1959 (Box Series I-4)
    American Folklore Society
  - Botkin, B.A., 1944 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bower, Blair T. (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, Taylor, Walter
  - Bowles, Gordon T., 1953 (Box Series I-4)
    -See also Ser. I, Dodge, Ernest Stanley
  - Boy Scouts of America, 1946-1947 (Box Series I-4)
    Swanton, John R.
  - Boyd, Julian P., 1948 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bradley, James W., 1987, 1992 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bragdon, Kathleen J., 1986 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brandhorst, Bob, 1968 (Box Series I-4)
    Alexander, Matt
    Parker, Judy
  - Brandon, William, 1968-1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brandreth, Courtenay, 1942 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brant Historical Society, 1942 (Box Series I-4)
  - Joseph Brant Museum, 1968-1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brantford Expositor, 1943, 1945, 1988 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brasser, Ted J., 1967-1974, n.d. (Box Series I-4)
    McGee, Dorothy H.
  - Bresson, Martine (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, Smith, Donald B.
  - Breuer, Ernest, 1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brew, J.O., 1948, 1958, 1961 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brewer, George E. (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, State University of New York at Albany
  - Bridges, Marjorie Lismer, 1939-1943 (Box Series I-4)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation, 1991 (Box Series I-4)
  - British Museum (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, Assembly of First Nations
  - Brock, R.W., 1910 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brock, Robin, 1994 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brockner, Winston William (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, Deardorff, Merle H. (1943)
  - Bronsdon, Madeline, 1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brooks, Anthony, Jr., 1989 (Box Series I-4)
    Erickson, John
    Spittal, William Guy
  - Broughton, John G., 1957-1977 (Box Series I-4)
    Butler, Mary
    Dodds, Christopher D.
    Flick, Hugh M.
    Hotchkiss, Nancy
    Indian Historian
    Kehoe, Thomas F.
    Snyder, Warren A.
    -See also Ser. I, Butler, Mary
    -See also Ser. I, Field Museum of Natural History
    -See also Ser. I, Robinson, Roy H.
    -See also Ser. I, Roseberry, [Cecil R.] "Tip"
    -See also Ser. I, Tooker, Elisabeth
  - Browman, David L., 1977 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Augustus F., 1948-1949 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, George W., 1946 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Harcourt, 1950 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Jennifer S.H., 1986 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Judith K., 1968-1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brown, Margaret, 1988 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bruce, Louis R., 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bruner, Laman H., Jr., 1965 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brunsteter, Della, 1939 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bryan, Mina R., 1955 (Box Series I-4)
  - Brydan, Sherry, 1994 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bucher, Bernadette, 1966 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buck, George J., 1941, 1947 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buck, Roy, 1951, 1959, 1971 (Box Series I-4)
  - Sir Peter Buck Memorial Recovery Trust, 1982 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bucknell University Christian Association, 1968 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buffalo Area Convention and Visitors Bureau, 1970 (Box Series I-4)
  - Buffalo Museum of Science, 1982-1984 (Box Series I-4)
  - Bulgheroni, Raul R., n.d. (Box Series I-4)
  - Bullard, William R., Jr. (Box Series I-4)
    -See Ser. I, Florida State Museum
  - Bunny, Thomas W., 1974 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burch, Wanda, 1992 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burdick, Usher L., 1946 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burke, Charles H., 1923 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burke, Ronald K., 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burns, Allan F., 1985 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burns, John William, 1984-1985 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burridge, K.O.L., 1974 (Box Series I-4)
  - Burrows, Edwin G., 1945 (Box Series I-4)
  - Butler, Mary, 1939-1940, 1968 (Box Series I-4)
    Broughton, John G.
    Funk, Robert E.
    Ritchie, William A.
    -See also Ser. I, Broughton, John G.
  - Butterfield, Lyman H., 1953, 1956, 1972 (Box Series I-4)
    -See also Ser. I, Institute of Early American History and Culture
  - Byers, A. Martin, 1971 (Box Series I-4)
  - Byers, Douglas S., 1941-1968 (Box Series I-4)
    Johnson, Frederick
    -See also Ser. I, American Antiquity
  - Byrne, Desmond, 1969 (Box Series I-4)
  - Cadbury, Warder H., 1987 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cadzow, Donald A. (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser. I, Deardorff, Merle H. (1947-1948)
    -See Ser. I, Pennsylvania Historical Commission
    -See Ser. I, Society for Pennsylvania Archaeology
  - Caedmon Records, Inc., 1963 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cairns, Huntington, 1947 (Box Series I-5)
  - Calapai, Letterio, 1947 (Box Series I-5)
  - Caldwell, Joseph R. (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser. I, Grassmann, Thomas
  - Calloway, Colin G., 1991 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cameron, Duncan F., 1968-1971 (Box Series I-5)
    -See also Ser. I, Glenbow Museum
  - Camp, William G., 1942 (Box Series I-5)
  - Campbell, Frank, 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Campbell, Lyle R., 1976 (Box Series I-5)
  - Campisi, Jack, 1971, 1994 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canada Council, 1974 (Box Series I-5)
    -See also Ser. I, Barbeau, C. Marius
  - Canada. Customs, 1945 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canada. Indian Affairs, 1933, 1939-1940 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canada. National Revenue, 1945 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canada. Province of British Columbia Archives, 1985 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canada. Public Archives, 1939, 1985 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canada. Treaties and Historical Research Centre, 1977 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation, 1945 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canadian Geographical Journal, 1943 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canadian Museum of Civilization, 1988-1992 (Box Series I-5)
    -See also Ser. I, National Museum of Man
  - Canadian Social Science Research Council, 1945 (Box Series I-5)
  - Canoe Island Lodge, 1965 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cantor, Nathaniel, 1940, 1944, 1956 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cantril, Hadley, 1945 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cappon, Lester J. (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser. I, Institute of Early American History and Culture
  - Cardinal, Jare R., 1982, 1992 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cardinal Lithographers, Inc., 1975 (Box Series I-5)
    American Museum of Natural History
  - Cardy, Michael, 1987 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carey, Hugh, 1977 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlen, Robert, 1970 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlisle, David B., 1973 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carlson, Norman P., 1987, 1991-1992 (Box Series I-5)
    includes some of WNF's Chautauqua notes
  - Carmer, Carl, 1943, 1959 (Box Series I-5)
    -See also Ser. I, Association on American Indian Affairs, Inc.
  - Carnahan, John W., 1972 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1968 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carnegie Museum, 1956, 1965-1966 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carnell, Prentiss III, 1965 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carpenter, Edmund S., 1941-1991 (Box Series I-5)
    -See also Ser. I, Blankenship, Roy
  - Carr, Lloyd G., 1944 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carrière, Joseph-M., 1947 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carse, Mary King Rowell, 1942-1949 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, Conrad P. (Mrs.), 1941 (Box Series I-5)
  - Carter, George F., 1945-1946 (Box Series I-5)
  - Casagrande, Joseph B., 1957 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cassidy, William (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser. I, Taylor, William
  - Cassie, Don R., 1969-1971 (Box Series I-5)
  - Cayuga County Historical Society, 1940-1989 (Box Series I-5)
    Drummond, Richard C.S.
    Groat, Charles V.
    Long, Walter K.
  - Cayuga Museum of History and Art (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser. I, Cayuga County Historical Society
  - Ceci, Lynn, 1968, 1977-1987, n.d. (Box Series I-5)
  - Central States Anthropological Society, 1971 (Box Series I-5)
    Lurie, Nancy Oestreich
    Ritzenthaler, Robert
  - Chabot, Huguette, 1969-1970 (Box Series I-5)
  - Chafe, Wallace L., 1960-1969, 1982 (Box Series I-5)
    -See also Ser. I, Foster, Michael K.
    -See also Ser. I, Kurath, Gertrude Prokosch
  - Chalmers, Harvey II (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser. I, American Historical Review
  - Chamberlain, Dudley, 1949 (Box Series I-5)
  - Champlain Society, 1976-1981 (Box Series I-5)
    Bell, R. Murray
    Warkentin, John
    -See also Ser. I, Moore, Elizabeth L.
  - Champlin, John H. (Box Series I-5)
    -See Ser. I, Congdon, Charles E.
  - Chapman, Ellwood B. (Box Series I-6)
    -See Ser. I, Pennsylvania Parks Association
  - Chapman, Thomas P., Jr., 1947 (Box Series I-6)
  - Chappell, Robert A., 1962 (Box Series I-6)
  - Charles, Prince of Wales (Box Series I-6)
    -See Ser. I, Treaty and Aboriginal Rights Research Centre of Manitoba, Inc.
  - Chatfield, Jennifer, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Chautauqua Institution, 1940, 1992 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cherokee-Iroquois Conference, 1978-1979 (Box Series I-6)
    -See also Ser. IIa, same title
  - Chew, Wilford, 1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Chicago Natural History Museum, 1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Chilcote, Lee A., 1990 (Box Series I-6)
  - Chinard, Gilbert, 1952 (Box Series I-6)
  - Chinese Art Society of America, 1944 (Box Series I-6)
    Scope and Conetents note
    Cox, Warren E.
  - Chodowiec, Urszula (Box Series I-6)
    -See Ser. I, Baligadoo, Urszula Chodowiec
  - Christie, T. Laird, 1980-1983 (Box Series I-6)
  - Ciborski, Sara, 1989 (Box Series I-6)
  - City of Liverpool Museums, 1969-1971 (Box Series I-6)
    Hunt, Charles
    Priestley, E.J.
    Priestman, K.B.
  - Clark, Austin H., 1950-1951 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clarke, T. Wood, 1940 (Box Series I-6)
  - Clarkin, William, 1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cline, Walter, 1946 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cloud, Wilton (Mrs.) [Alta], 1955 (Box Series I-6)
    Stevens, Bertha
  - Coates, Robert M., 1968 (Box Series I-6)
  - Coatsworth, Emerson S., 1951-1953 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cochran, Gertrude, 1990 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cochrane, Ruth Hale, 1985 (Box Series I-6)
    Hartley, Erma Hale
  - Coe, Stephen H., 1968-1970 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cohen, Felix S., 1949-1950 (Box Series I-6)
    Nichols, John R.
    Snyderman, George S.
    -See also Ser. I, Snyderman, George
  - Cohen, Hennig, 1960 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cold Spring Longhouse, 1955 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cole, Douglas, 1985 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cole, Fay-Cooper, 1958 (Box Series I-6)
    -See also Ser. I, Kidder, Alfred V. II
  - Coleman, R.V., 1949-1950 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collamer, Jeanette R., 1972, 1974 (Box Series I-6)
    Rochester Museum and Science Center
    -See also Ser. I, Rochester Museum and Science Center
  - Collier, Donald, 1964 (Box Series I-6)
    -See also Ser. I, Council for Museum Anthropology
  - Collier, John (Box Series I-6)
    -See Ser. I, United States. Dept. of the Interior
  - Collier, John, Jr., 1963 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collier, Robert S., 1994 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Arthur, 1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Donald L., 1957 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Evan R., 1968 (Box Series I-6)
  - Collins, Henry B., 1962 (Box Series I-6)
  - Colonial Williamsburg, 1953, 1965 (Box Series I-6)
    -See also Ser. I, United States. Dept. of the Interior
  - Colonie Central High School, 1961 (Box Series I-6)
  - Columbia University, 1977 (Box Series I-6)
  - Commager, Henry S., 1962 (Box Series I-6)
  - Commentary, 1949 (Box Series I-6)
  - Commerford, Lester, 1951 (Box Series I-6)
  - Committee on Anthropological Research in Museums, 1970-1972 (Box Series I-6)
  - Compton Brothers Co., 1954 (Box Series I-6)
  - Compton's Pictured Encyclopedia, 1950 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conable, Barber B., Jr., 1983-1993 (Box Series I-6)
    Congdon, Lillian
  - Conable, Daniel B., 1969 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conant, Lawrence M., 1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conard, A. Mark, 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Condominas, Georges, 1972-1973, 1976 (Box Series I-6)
  - Congdon, Charles E. (Box Series I-6)
    Champlin, John H.
    Congdon, Richard Bell
    Congdon, William J.
    Cornplanter, Jesse J. (1942)
    Edwards, William Waller
    Havighurst, Walter
    Lewis, Ralph H.
    Reed, Daniel A.
    -See also Ser. I, Deardorff, Merle
    -See also Ser. I, Ritchie, William
    - Folder #1, 1938-1943 (Box Series I-6)
    - Folder #2, 1944-1974 (Box Series I-6)
  - Congdon, Elizabeth, 1948, 1951 (Box Series I-6)
  - Congdon, Lillian, 1987 (Box Series I-6)
    -See also Ser. I, Conable, Barber, Jr.
  - Congdon, Richard Bell, 1941-1942, 1965-1969 (Box Series I-6)
    Sharp, Lauriston
    -See also Ser. I, Congdon, Charles E.
  - Congdon, William J. (Box Series I-6)
  - Conklin, Harold C., 1942-1950, 1969-1991 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conklin, Jean, 1991 (Box Series I-6)
  - Conklin, May, 1944, 1947-1948 (Box Series I-6)
  - Connecticut College, [1969] (Box Series I-6)
  - Conservationist, 1954 (Box Series I-6)
  - Cook, Bill, 1946 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cook, Charles, 1990 (Box Series I-7)
    Tonko, Paul
  - Cook, William J. (Box Series I-7)
  - Cookenham, Walt, Jr., 1974 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cooper, G. Arthur, 1944 (Box Series I-7)
    -See also Ser. I, Weslager, C.A.
  - Cooper, John M., 1936-1945 (Box Series I-7)
    DuRand, Elden E.
  - Cooper, Leroy, 1934 (Box Series I-7)
  - Corey, Albert B., 1946 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cornehlson, John H., Jr., 1948 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cornelius, Carol, 1991 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cornelius, Laura M., 1906 (Box Series I-7)
    Maxon, S.A.
  - Cornell University, 1944, 1971, 1980, 1989 (Box Series I-7)
  - Corning, Erastus II, 1965-1981 (Box Series I-7)
    Beachamp, William M.
  - Cornplanter, Edward, 1897-1914 (Box Series I-7)
    -See also Ser. I, Cornplanter, Nancy
  - Cornplanter, Elsina, 1956 (Box Series I-7)
  - Cornplanter, Jesse J. (Box Series I-7)
    Bartholomew, David
    Bartlett, Charles E.
    Bartlett, Sally (1955)
    Bigler, Eugene (1951)
    Burke, Charles H.
    Conklin, Harold C.
    Cook, William J.
    Gabor, Robert G.
    Gruber, Jacob W.
    Mynter, Kenneth H.
    Pollenz, Philippa
    Ripken, Henry E. (Mrs.)
    Westez, Carlos
    -See also Ser. I, Burke, Charles
    -See also Ser. I, Congdon, Charles
    -See also Ser. I, Harrington, John
    -See also Ser. I, Hastings, Glover Street II
    -See also Ser. I, Hauptman, Laurence Marc
    -See also Ser. I, Henricks, Walter A. (Mrs.)
    -See also Ser. I, Hewitt, J.N.B.
    -See also Ser. I, Parker, Arthur C.
    -See also Ser. I, Pollenz, Philippa
    -See also Ser. I, Risley, Marius
    -See also Ser. I, Wissler, Clark
    - Folder #1, 1900-1935 (Box Series I-7)
    - Folder #2, 1936-1942 (Box Series I-7)
    - Folder #3, 1943-1947 (Box Series I-7)
    - Folder #4, 1948-1949 (Box Series I-7)
    - Folder #5, 1950-1951 (Box Series I-7)
    - Folder #6, 1952-1953 (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder #7, 1954-1955 (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder #8, 1956-1957, n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Cornplanter, Jesse J.--Originals (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder #1, 1904-1944 (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder #2, 1945-1949 (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder #3, 1950-1954 (Box Series I-8)
    - Folder #4, 1955-1957, n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Cornplanter, Nancy, 1902 (Box Series I-8)
  - Cosmos Club, 1945, 1954, 1987 (Box Series I-8)
    Lowenthal, Max
    Oehser, Paul H.
    University of Oklahoma Press
  - Costa, Richard H., 1982 (Box Series I-8)
  - Coste, Ann R. (Box Series I-8)
  - Costikyan, Edward N., 1991 (Box Series I-8)
    Kornblau, David L.
    Paul, Weiss, [et al.]
  - Cotter, John L., 1969 (Box Series I-8)
  - Council for Museum Anthropology, 1974-1975 (Box Series I-8)
    University of Pennsylvania. University Museum
    -See also Ser. I, Committee on Anthropological Research in Museums
  - Council of Indians in Canada, 1965 (Box Series I-8)
  - Council on Anthropology and Education, 1969 (Box Series I-8)
    Gearing, Frederick O.
  - Countryman, Edward, 1989 (Box Series I-9)
  - Covey, Barbara L., 1972 (Box Series I-9)
  - Cowan, J. Milton (Box Series I-9)
    -See Ser. I, UNESCO
  - Cowan, William, 1984-1987 (Box Series I-9)
    Koerner, Konrad
  - Cox, Warren E., 1939, 1944 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser. I, Chinese Art Society of America
  - Cranbrook Institute of Science, 1942-1984 (Box Series I-9)
  - Crane, Theodore R., 1952 (Box Series I-9)
  - Crary, John C., Jr., 1959 (Box Series I-9)
  - Cronk, Michael Sam, 1993 (Box Series I-9)
  - Cross, Michael S., 1977 (Box Series I-9)
  - Crossette, George, 1974 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser. I, Oehser, Paul H.
  - Crouse, Dorothy, 1956-1958 (Box Series I-9)
  - Crouse, Florence (Box Series I-9)
    -See Ser. I, Redeye, Clara
  - Crouse, Myrtle, 1959 (Box Series I-9)
    -Deardorff, Merle H.
  - Crouse, Wilford (Mrs.), 1939 (Box Series I-9)
  - Crow, James, 1941, n.d. (Box Series I-9)
  - Crowe, Patrick J., 1993 (Box Series I-9)
  - Crowell, Marnie Reed, 1973 (Box Series I-9)
    Einhorn, Arthur
  - Crowley, Thomas J., 1967-1968 (Box Series I-9)
  - Cummings, John, 1956 (Box Series I-9)
  - Cunard, Sherwyn, 1972 (Box Series I-9)
  - Cunningham, Wells, 1949 (Box Series I-9)
  - Curley, Richard, 1968 (Box Series I-9)
  - Dallaire, Louise (Box Series I-9)
    -See Ser. I, National Museum of Man
    -See Ser. I, Woodbury, Hanni
  - Dalton, Ernest R., 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - D'Amato, Alfonse, 1981 (Box Series I-9)
  - Damkoehler, Julia E., 1994 (Box Series I-9)
  - Daniel, Warren J., 1945 (Box Series I-9)
  - Dark, Philip J.C., 1969, 1972 (Box Series I-9)
  - Darnell, Regna, 1969-1984 (Box Series I-9)
  - Dartmouth College, 1931-1992 (Box Series I-9)
    DeGrange, McQuilkin
    Goddard, Richard H.
    Hanson, A.H.
    Hayward, Sidney Chandler
    McFarland, Alex J.
    McKennan, Robert A.
  - Dartmouth College Library, 1939-1989 (Box Series I-9)
    Goodrich, Nathaniel L.
    Rugg, Harold G.
    West, Herbert Faulkner
  - Daughton, Kathy, 1966 (Box Series I-9)
    Fremming, Barbara
    Davenport, William H.
    -See Ser. I, University of Pennsylvania. University Museum
  - The David Livingston Centre, 1994 (Box Series I-9)
  - Davidson, D. Sutherland, 1935, 1943 (Box Series I-9)
    -See also Ser. I, American Folklore Society, Inc.
  - Davidson, Herbert, 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Davis, Duane, 1989 (Box Series I-9)
  - Davis, E. Mott, 1953 (Box Series I-9)
  - Davis, Harold E., 1939-1946 (Box Series I-9)
  - Davis, Joseph C., 1968 (Box Series I-9)